ROBERT ZACCHIGNA

About - Robert-Zacchigna.github.io | Contact - Robert-Zacchigna.github.io

SUMMARY



Over 4 years of IT experience, just over 2.5 years of professional experience working for Discover Financial Services as a Data Engineer developing pipelines for cloud technologies and 2 years working for Illinois State University as a System Administrator managing various enterprise applications. I am also a member of the National Society of Collegiate Scholars (NSCS).

EDUCATION

June 2019 –

Bellevue University, Graduating November 2021, Current GPA: 4.0

Nov 2021

Masters Of Science - Data Science

August 2015 – May 2019 *Illinois State University*

Bachelors in Information Technology – Systems Development/Analytics

Minor in Business – Business Administration

TECHNOLOGY

Languages

· Python/Spark/Kafka · R

HTML/Javascript/Jekyll

·SQL/NoSQL · Java

Software

· Linux/Unix

PyCharm

AWS (Some Experience)

Tensorflow/Keras

RStudio

· Snowflake/Teradata · Visual Studio

EXPERIENCE

June 2019 – Present

Data Engineer, Discover Financial Services (DFS)

• Currently working as a Data engineer at DFS. Main projects includes onboarding business users to cloud technologies to help develop pipelines to allow them to access the data that they need using cloud-based tools.

August 2017 – May 2019

System Administrator, Illinois State University at Administrative Technologies (AT)

· While attending the university, I worked part-time as a Sys Admin for AT maintaining (users, security, app updating, etc.) different apps used throughout the university.

May 2017 – August 2017

System Administrator Intern, Illinois State University at Administrative Technologies (AT)

• System Administrator role; learned about the various apps the university uses and how to properly maintain and handle security for each app.